const integrals = [
    { question: "∫ 1 dx", answer: "x" },
    { question: "∫ 2 dx", answer: "2x" },
    { question: "∫ 5 dx", answer: "5x" },
    { question: "∫ x dx", answer: "x^2/2" },
    { question: "∫ 3x dx", answer: "3x^2/2" },
    { question: "∫ x^2 dx", answer: "x^3/3" },
    { question: "∫ x^3 dx", answer: "x^4/4" },
    { question: "∫ 4x dx", answer: "2x^2" },
    { question: "∫ 1/x dx", answer: "ln|x|" },
    { question: "∫ e^x dx", answer: "e^x" },
    { question: "∫ cos(x) dx", answer: "sin(x)" },
    { question: "∫ sin(x) dx", answer: "-cos(x)" },
    { question: "∫ 2x dx", answer: "x^2" },
    { question: "∫ 1/(x+1) dx", answer: "ln|x+1|" },
    { question: "∫ x dx (from 0 to 2)", answer: "2" },
    { question: "∫ 7 dx", answer: "7x" },
    { question: "∫ 5 dx", answer: "5x" },
    { question: "∫ 4x^2 dx", answer: "4x^3/3" },
    { question: "∫ 6 dx", answer: "6x" },
    { question: "∫ x^2 dx (from 0 to 2)", answer: "8/3" },
];


const derivatives = [
    { question: "d/dx (x^2)", answer: "2x" },
    { question: "d/dx (x^3)", answer: "3x^2" },
    { question: "d/dx (x^4)", answer: "4x^3" },
    { question: "d/dx (sin(x))", answer: "cos(x)" },
    { question: "d/dx (cos(x))", answer: "-sin(x)" },
    { question: "d/dx (e^x)", answer: "e^x" },
    { question: "d/dx (ln(x))", answer: "1/x" },
    { question: "d/dx (x^5)", answer: "5x^4" },
    { question: "d/dx (x)", answer: "1" },
    { question: "d/dx (x^2 + 3)", answer: "2x" },
    { question: "d/dx (x + 5)", answer: "1" },
    { question: "d/dx (x^2 + x)", answer: "2x + 1" },
    { question: "d/dx (2x^2)", answer: "4x" },
    { question: "d/dx (x^3 - x)", answer: "3x^2 - 1" },
    { question: "d/dx (3x)", answer: "3" },
    { question: "d/dx (5x^2)", answer: "10x" },
    { question: "d/dx (x^2 + 2x)", answer: "2x + 2" },
    { question: "d/dx (2x)", answer: "2" },
    { question: "d/dx (5x^3)", answer: "15x^2" },
    { question: "d/dx (x^2 + 4)", answer: "2x" },
];

